The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove back to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
The Clover Kingdom.
It's the Clover Kingdom.
Well done.
This isn't the way I made it.
I really love you so much.
Yeah.
When I have jest here, my stomach thinks same as I feel.
Please, let me go to the other side.
I was trained if I guess they won't delay it.
I got a писar bullet for a kidney.
The sixth day, every hmm is ready to hurt.
launcher
on
Mah
he
It's in the heart of the kingdom! The one with all the hearts!
Stop acting all squirrely and try to make some sense! Think about what you say!
We got Gordon's dad to help us look around for big curses and he found a stupidly huge one right in the middle of the heart kingdom, okay?
Huh?
I'm pretty sure it's a devil's curse. I mean, it's gotta be right, so that's where I wanna go next!
Where's your pal Gordon? What does he think about this?
He wanted to learn some curse magic from his dad, so he decided to stay home a little longer.
Alright, fine. Now wanna tell me why the two of them look like they just had their brains scrambled?
I think it's because of the food they were given, but I'm fine. Actually, I thought it was great!
Fair enough. I think I'm up to speed.
Cool! So can I go to the heart kingdom?
Sure. Just sit tight for now. I'll look into it.
It's not happening.
Huh?
Apparently the heart kingdom can't be entered.
Are you serious, sir?
I was planning to go there too. That's where we'll find the next clue we need. I'm sure of it.
Well, the borders are tight. The entire length of it has been rigged with a bunch of trap spells. Trip one and we'll be wanted criminals. Might spark an international incident.
No way. Wait, why don't we just destroy the traps with my anti-magic and sneak in that way?
Because that's dumb, they'll sense the traps disappearing.
Oh.
Well, that's troublesome. Not even Rouge's power could get you through there undetected.
Whatever we try, they'll notice.
Wait! There has to be some way. Because I heard Mimosa say that she'd been there before.
Whoa, really?
It's true. She said there was some sort of student exchange program between our nobility and theirs.
Alright, Finral. Take these twerps to the Golden Dawn's base.
Kay!
Uh, Finral? I'm kinda confused. Why aren't you complaining about getting used as an errand boy?
Because I'm excited. There's someone I wanted to see there.
Believe it or not, it was your brother Finral who managed to stop you in the end.
Arrogant jerk.
Longris! Hey! I heard you finally woke up! I'm really glad!
So you came.
Hello, Finral.
Lady Finnis! I'm glad you're well.
Must be satisfying.
Huh?
I tried to murder my own brother, but found myself defeated.
Then, as my parents desperately apologized for me, I tried to murder my king.
I guess I'm the one who's a disgrace to the family name now.
Wait! What are you saying? That was only because you were possessed by an elf! Everyone will understand-
And, worst of all, it was you who saved me.
Uh...
I heard all about your squadmate's trial. Both you and that commoner. You're insufferable.
You don't have any talent. And yet you've still managed to outdo me somehow.
This isn't over yet. Understand?
Yeah! That's the spirit! This just confirms that I'm right to declare war on you.
Huh?
Starting now, I'll work hard, prove myself to father, and become the kind of man who deserves to lead our house.
Also, I'll be the man who makes Lady Finnis happy.
I'm sorry to drag you into this, Lady Finnis, but I promise, once I've become worthy, I'm gonna come back for you.
I guess I'm willing to wait, but don't take too long, okay?
Let's take a walk, brother.
Huh? Should you be moving right now?
I have to ask you to wait here, Lady Finnis.
Don't worry, I'm not planning to fill him with holes again.
Whoa, Longress, too soon.
What's up? Is something the matter?
Unless you transform drastically, you'll have no chance of making Lady Finnis happy.
Here's why.
Why?
Hello, Vice Captain Longress.
You're feeling well enough to get out of bed now, sir?
Oh, yeah! What cloud did you angels fall from? Some babes are just too hot for heaven!
Just as I expected.
It's plain to see that you're cursed!
What?!
You hit on every girl you meet like a wannabe playboy!
Playboy?!
And the time you spent shirking your duties made you an even bigger failure than ever!
That free-willing life has left you with bad habits that won't just break!
There's no way a self-centered degenerate like you could make Lady Finnis happy!
Ah!
Yeah, you're totally right.
Sorry if we're interrupting whatever this is.
I heard the Vice Captain's been acting strangely ever since he woke.
Make sure you do your level best to rid yourself of that curse. If you can't pull it off, I might end up marrying Lady Finnis myself.
Wait! So was breaking my curse part of this investigation too?
Huh.
I won't let you get your happy ending that easily, brother.
I understand now. You need to get inside.
Anything to help Asta.
It's true that I've been to the Heart Kingdom. I was around 13 at the time.
My brother and I were both sent over as exchange students. Though I would have preferred different company.
We were only allowed access to a limited area, but I still learned a lot. Their magic's amazing.
The techniques they use are like nothing you would find here in Clover.
The Heart Kingdom is a verdant land through which water is always flowing, and its rich environment generates a tremendous amount of mana.
If you're right in saying that what lies at the center of it is a devil-induced curse, then we have cause to be scared.
Although it's honestly hard to believe.
A devil's curse. This could give me a clue about the devil that Mother encountered.
We weren't allowed to meet her, but I was told that the queen who rules over the Heart Kingdom is every bit as powerful as one of our magic knight squads.
They say that she's an all-knowing mage who sees everything that happens in her kingdom.
No way! Whoa! A queen, huh? If she's like the Witch Queen, then we might be in trouble.
Well, we're not going over there to pick a fight, so it's fine. I'll just keep my guard up.
I believe they're accepting applications to visit as we speak. I'll see if I can get us all permission to go.
Thanks a bunch, Mimosa!
It's huge! I've never seen such an enormous ship in my life!
It's actually on the smaller side, but it does look nice!
Calm down, Osta. This isn't a vacation.
You never told us that you owned your own ship, Captain. Did you pick it up recently? Or what?
Well, I met with Julius' helper and made a few threats. You were up compelling points and he lent it to us.
Huh?
If you damage it, I'll kill you hard.
Right!
Osta, be careful. Protect Mimosa.
You have nothing to worry about, Klaus. We're making this trip to investigate something, not to fight.
But still, if something should happen while you're out there, we won't be able to come to your aid. I'd feel much better about this if I could go along too.
Well, there's only four spots. First up's Osta, the royal from the Golden Dawn who arranged all of this.
Noelle, who looks none too willing to give up her spot. And then Finral.
Yeah, Captain. Why'd you want me to be the fourth anyway?
Cuz having wheels tends to come in handy. Agreed?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, there's no arguing with that logic.
You said it. He is quite convenient.
I get it. Spatial magic is nice to have, but he's really just a pack mule.
You know what? You don't need to understand!
Osta, go kick some ass in the Heart Kingdom for me.
You better not.
Right! Take care of things there and come home soon, okay? The two of us still need to have a duel, Osta! Right!
If you get homesick and can't sleep, just take a swig of this stuff and you'll pass right out.
Mm-hmm. You're underage, Osta.
Okay, you've all said your goodbyes. Now stop wasting time. You've got a job of your own to do.
Yeah, yeah, we remember!
Let's do this!
Later!
You scram, too. Try to stay on your toes out there.
Right!
Two thousand thirty-one! Two thousand thirty-two! Two thousand thirty-three! Two thousand thirty-four! Two thousand thirty-five!
Stay cool
I don't think I'm gonna be able to sleep at night. Oh, come on
It's not much, but I hope you enjoy it you made all this yourself looks tasty
Okay
bother me
Here have some water
There now thank me. I'm not grateful. You scared me. That water almost put me into the ocean. I don't get why this bothers me
What the heck am I watching right now?
More important than me drowning
Check it out we finally made it you guys who would have thought we could just enter the kingdom legally once again asta
We aren't here on vacation
I'm sorry that I wasn't able to get permission for anyone else to come
Nah, don't worry about it
I'm nothing but grateful to you for getting us in and if we need help we can use thin real spatial magic gonna get us all arrested
Whoa, why did it get so foggy all of a sudden it's one of the heart kingdom's defense measures
No vessel can pass through this fog unless it's permitted to by the queen
Oh
I couldn't sleep a wink last night knowing I was surrounded by beautiful girls
Damn it. Now. I'm wondering what the queen of heart kingdom looks like. Is she hot too?
She must be the heart kingdoms just ahead. I can't wait to see it
So this is the place the heart kingdom it all blends together city forest and water so cool
Their ship is arriving right on schedule the clover kingdoms devil has significant power power that we must obtain
Huh, I guess you could say it's pretty where do you think we're supposed to tie up the boat
Please continue sailing forward wait
Allow me to welcome you to our kingdom. I'm the spirit guardian gaja and I will act as your guide while you're here
Is he important? He sure seems to be
It's been quite a while lady mimosa you and I met the last time you visited
It's lovely to see you gaja. I consider it an honor that you remember me
How could I forget you were well liked by everyone who made your acquaintance my lady
Spirit guardian gaja meet my friends asta noel and finral. It's a pleasure to meet you
Would you care to try some crimson horse juice you can use mana to sweeten it
For you. Thank you very much
What is this stuff it's fantastic
Mine tastes super bitter noel would you run some of your mana through it for me
No, if you're gonna beg then fine you told us to keep sailing forward, but this looks like a dead end fear not
The queen will guide your ship onward
Whoa
So it's the queen who's moving us all of this is being controlled by one mage
Both the mist barrier and the water stairs are products of the queen's monozone which spans across the entire kingdom
That's awesome. And so is this weird red juice of yours
He can't be serious it covers the whole kingdom is that really possible
Even the butterflies are extra pretty here
This truly is a lovely kingdom
It's hard to believe that there's a devil here
Our kingdom was founded 1200 years ago
Since then our queens have also acted as priestesses
Forming packs with the spirit undeened to gain its strength
This is a country of water and life
We steward the land and it rewards us with mana
Enough to keep out any unwanted guests
Incredible to think that one queen is able to protect the whole country through peaceful means
Yes, that's been the case so far
But the future is uncertain even to our queen
Asta!
How could you?
Just what do you think you're doing, Gaja?
We need his help to protect the peace we've cultivated here
We have to go after him
Leave it to me
Don't slow down, Mimosa
Put your faith in our transporter
Right
Spacial magic falling in with wingbeat
Ah, it's only about a third stage, but still
You have some rather intriguing magic
Look out!
Water creation magic
Sea dragon flare
How's he floating without using any spells?
I don't know what you're trying to pull
But you have just abducted the friend of a clover kingdom royal
And that action has consequences
Yeah, Noelle, that's my girl!
A cute face and a cold stare
What am I saying? Lady Phenis is the only girl for me!
Her magic is both rare and powerful
Definitely first stage
That's some remarkable water magic you have
If you aren't holding back, then I won't either
What kind of spell is this?
I'm sorry for treating you so roughly
But I must protect my country
And it has need of your devil
Where the heck did that weird bubble take me?
Is that the heart kingdom's queen talking?
Because if so
Stop!
His attribute is lightning?
Then what's the deal with those runes he makes?
It looks like he's using a type of magic unique to the heart kingdom
Lightning magic
Tengiolia
It's fast, but my Valkyrie armor is faster
She truly is a first stage
But
My spell has orders
It will give pursuit until it strikes its target
Please, Gaja!
Bring our friend back right now!
Refuse and we'll have no recourse but to fight!
An attack spell
It seems Lady Mimosa has become a third stage herself
As for the Spatial Mage
It looks like he can make a portal between any two points he has sight of
Allow me to show you a brief glimpse of the difference in our strength
He cast it into the sky?
So much power
Nature itself supplies me with mana
No human can match its might
I can't keep this up forever
Just how much mana does this lady have?
Besides, why are we even fighting anyway?
So that's your Devil's power
Magic negation
What the?
Abominable as that is, it also sounds quite useful
Pleased to meet you, Devil Possessed Child from Clover
You may address me as Undine
I'm one of the four great spirits and I'm contracted to the Queen of the Heart Kingdom
You are quite impressive
But that doesn't mean you're any match for me
Intriguing
You don't have any magic of your own, do you?
Why, that puts you even beneath the Ninth Stage
The Ninth Stage?
The heck are you talking about?
Oh, that's right
There isn't a system to quantify magic strength in your kingdom, is there?
The weakest mages are of the Ninth Stage
The Eighth are above them, and the Seventh above them
Our system shows which mages have the most talent
I can't move
Or breathe
Care to guess which stage is the highest?
It's Stage Zero
True lightning magic
Muriel Astroza
If they were still within sight, I'd be able to sense their mana
They must have fled with Spatial Magic
A wise choice
But no matter where they try to hide
He created a portal to a place you couldn't see
Plant Creation Magic
Magic Flower Guide
This is Spatial Magic
Fallen Angel Gate
Here's the deal
We can't just back down after watching you show off
Water Creation Magic
Sea Dragon's Roar
Your system's trash
You can't measure ability just by looking at talent
Feeling Magic Inverse Relief
This magic
I'll keep my anti-magic all around me so she can't pull me in again
I can feel a person's key just ahead of me
And if there's a human up there
Then there must be
Air
Mind if I join you?
I can feel highly un sauve
I forgot everything
If you are ready to loose
When you are going back
I think I will do
I don't have anything
at any time
We'll be right back.
129, The Devil Megicula, in which Queen Laura Pechka appears.